Guide to the Merle Hoffman Papers, circa 1944-2012 and undated, bulk 1961-2000 RL.00557
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Choices Series, 1945-2000 and undated, bulk 1976-2000, 48 boxes
  - Operations Subseries, 1970-2000 and undated
    - Facilities, 1977-1998 and undated
      - 1994, Lease amendment (Box CH32)
      - 1995, Architects' proposal (Box CH32)
      - 1995, Environmental survey, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH32)
      - 1995, Environmental survey, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH33)
      - 1995-1996, New location search (Box CH33)
      - 1996, Correspondence on return of good-faith deposit (Box CH33)
      - 1996, Environmental survey (Box CH33)
      - 1997, DiGiorgio Associates architects dispute (Box CH33)
      - 1997-1998 and undated, Relocation planning, new letterhead and new office signs (Box CH33)
      - 1998, Lease negotiations (Box CH33)
      - 1998, Moving - Bridge Plaza (Box CH33)
      - 1998, Moving history (Box CH33)
      - 1998, New address announcement design. (Box CH33)
    - Mental Health, 1992-1998 and undated
      - 1992-1994 and undated, Rape Treatment Program (Box CH33)
      - 1992-1994, Rape Treatment Program reports and procedures (Box CH33)
      - 1994 and undated, Rape Treatment Program Manual
        - Case review meetings (Box CH33)
        - Fees and finances (Box CH33)
        - Policies and procedures (Box CH33)
      - 1992-1994, Rape Treatment Program staff meeting minutes (Box CH34)
      - 1995-1996, Client profiles, Advisory Council meeting and radio campaign (Box CH34)
      - 1995-1996, Mental Health HMO/PPO meeting minutes (Box CH34)
      - 1995-1999, Advisory Council meetings (Box CH34)
      - 1996 Aug. 22, HMO mailing list for paradigm letters (Box CH34)
      - 1996, Disorder of Intimacy paradigm - manual (Box CH34)
      - 1998, Annual report (Box CH34)
      - 1990s, Disorders of Intimacy paradigm and procedures (Box CH34)
      - 1990s, Mission statement (Box CH34)
    - New York Government, 1970-1998 and undated
      - 1970-1977 and undated, City health code excerpts (Box CH34)
      - 1976-1983, Department of Health operating certificates (Box CH34)
      - 1977-1987, City Department of Health - labwork proficiency tests (Box CH34)
      - 1979, City Department of Health - site visit report (Box CH34)
      - 1981-1988 and undated, Department of Health - outstanding issues (Box CH34)
      - 1982-1983 and undated, City Department of Health - site visit (Box CH35)
      - 1983-1986, Department of Health, Capital Problem and Service Needs Assessment Inventory (Box CH35)
      - 1985-1993, Application for D and C program approval, 4 folders (Box CH35)
      - 1985-1989 and 1993, Department of Health - operating certificates (Box CH35)
      - 1985, 1992-1995 and undated, Medicaid correspondence and procedures (Box CH35)
      - 1986-1990 and undated, City Department of Health - labwork proficiency tests (Box CH35)
      - 1987, Department of Health D and C - policies and procedures manual (Box CH35)
      - 1987, Department of Health - Plan of Corrections notebook, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box CH35)
      - 1987, Department of Health - Plan of Corrections notebook, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box CH36)
      - 1987-1989, City Department of Health - vasectomy survey (Box CH36)
      - 1988-1990, Department of Health - incident reports and notice of legal proceedings (Box CH36)
      - 1989, Department of Health - incident reports and correspondence (Box CH36)
      - 1989, Department of Health - Plan of Corrections notebook, 2 folders (Box CH36)
      - 1990, City Department of Health - laboratory plan of corrections (Box CH36)
      - 1990, City Department of Health - Reproductive Health Service Questionnaire (Box CH36)
      - 1990 and undated, Department of Health Prenatal Care Assistance Program policies (Box CH36)
      - 1991, Revisions of physician discipline mechanisms (Box CH36)
      - 1991-1992, Department of Health - Application for outpatient surgery reimbursement (Box CH36)
      - 1991 and 1994, Department of Health rape treatment and evidence collection rules (Box CH36)
      - 1992-1993, Department of Health - appeals (Box CH36)
      - 1992-1998 and undated, Medicaid Managed Care program (Box CH36)
      - 1993, Medicaid chart review (Box CH36)
      - 1993-1996, Medicaid Transportation Program (Box CH36)
      - 1994, City Department of Health - laboratory plan of corrections (Box CH36)
      - 1994, Medicaid claims reviews (Box CH36)
      - 1994, Medicaid review - appeal (Box CH37)
      - 1996 and undated, Medicaid censure and request for repayment (Box CH37)
      - 1997-1998, City Department of Health - STD reporting (Box CH37)
      - 1998, Department of Health - HIV case reporting (Box CH37)
    - Personnel, 1983-1999 and undated
      - 1983 and 1987-1988 and undated, In-service meeting minutes (Box CH37)
      - 1984 and 1990, Maternity leave policy (Box CH37)
      - 1987-1989, Personnel Policy and Procedures manual, 3 folders (Box CH37)
      - 1988-1989, In-service programs (Box CH37)
      - 1988-1996 and undated, Job descriptions (Box CH37)
      - 1989-1998, Employee manual revisions (Box CH37)
      - 1991-1992, Physician work schedules, 2 folders (Box CH37)
      - 1992, 1993, Holiday party, 2 folders (Box CH37)
      - 1993-1996, Supervisor work schedules (Box CH37)
      - 1993, In-service programs, 3 folders (Box CH38)
      - 1993, Physician work schedules (Box CH38)
      - 1993, Thanksgiving (Box CH38)
      - 1993, Weight Watchers at Work (Box CH38)
      - 1994, Employee orientation (Box CH38)
      - 1994, Nurse practitioner collaborative practice agreements (Box CH38)
      - 1994, Physician work schedules (Box CH38)
      - 1994 and undated, Job description manual (Box CH38)
      - 1994 and undated, Questionnaires (Box CH38)
      - 1994-1997 and undated, Holidays (Box CH38)
      - 1995, Staff parties (Box CH38)
      - 1995, Take a Girl to Work Day (Box CH38)
      - 1995-1996, Physician work schedules (Box CH38)
      - 1996, In-service programs (Box CH38)
      - 1996 and undated, Child care (Box CH38)
      - 1997, Holiday party (Box CH38)
      - 1997, Physician work schedules (Box CH38)
      - 1998 Jul. 22, Infection control and documentation in-service (Box CH38)
      - 1998, In-service attendance and materials, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH38)
      - 1998, In-service attendance and materials, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH39)
      - 1998, Job descriptions (Box CH39)
      - 1998, Language skills (Box CH39)
      - 1998, Physician work schedules (Box CH39)
      - 1999, Employee manual (Box CH39)
      - 1990s, Gynecology in-service program (Box CH39)
      - 1990s, Physician and therapist staff lists (Box CH39)
      - Undated, Counselor application questionnaire (Box CH39)
      - Undated, Patient Relations in-service program (Box CH39)
      - Undated, Physician employment contract drafts (Box CH39)
      - Undated, Physicians on staff (Box CH39)
      - Undated, Staff ads (Box CH39)
    - General Operations, 1972-2000 and undated
      - 1972, Alan Guttmacher Institute - site visit report (Box CH39)
      - 1975-1976, Business certificate and mortgage correspondence (Box CH39)
      - 1976-1994 and undated, Counseling and phone contact training materials (Box CH39)
      - 1978-1991, Service contracts (Box CH39)
      - 1981-1995, Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box CH39)
      - 1982-1986 and undated, Laboratory services (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1984, Facilitators staff meeting minutes (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1984, Meeting minutes (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1984, MPF [Appointments] staff meeting minutes (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1984, Nursing staff meeting minutes (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1984, Supervisors' meetings minutes (Box CH39)
      - 1983-1990, Medical Directors and Medical staff meetings minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1984, General Office Staff meeting minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1984-1985, Audit and evaluation - Touche Ross and Co. (Box CH40)
      - 1984-1985, Certificate of incorporation filing (Box CH40)
      - 1984-1988, Gynecology staff and Infection Control Committee meetings minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1984-1997, Organizational flow charts and staff lists (Box CH40)
      - 1985-1987, Financial records and application for stock transfer (Box CH40)
      - 1985-1989, Appointment room staff meeting minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1985-1989, Counseling staff meeting minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1985-1989, Nursing staff meeting minutes (Box CH40)
      - 1985-1989, Quality Assurance Committee minutes, 2 folders (Box CH40)
      - Supervisors' meetings minutes, 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box CH41)
      - 1986, D and C program meeting minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1987, Medical staff meeting minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1987, Planning Committee minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1989, Credentials Committee minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1989, Front desk staff meeting minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1989, Pharmacy Committee minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1991 and undated, Business Office - contract list, equipment, and patient census (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1997, Malpractice insurance, 2 folders (Box CH41)
      - 1986-1997, Dilepan (Box CH41)
      - 1987-1988, Second trimester abortion procedures (Box CH41)
      - 1987-1989, Medical records staff meeting and committee meetings - minutes (Box CH41)
      - 1987-1989, Planning meetings (Box CH41)
      - 1987-1990, Ultrasound equipment and review (Box CH41)
      - 1987-1994, Quality Assurance Committee (Box CH41)
      - 1988, Complication calls review (Box CH42)
      - 1988, HIV/AIDS protocols and memos (Box CH42)
      - 1988, Medical/Administrative Committee minutes (Box CH42)
      - 1988, No-smoking policy (Box CH42)
      - 1988-1990, Pre-natal care policies and patients (Box CH42)
      - 1988-1990, Telephone appointments, staff meeting minutes and phone log (Box CH42)
      - 1988-1996, Ambulance services (Box CH42)
      - 1988-1998, Answering service (Box CH42)
      - 1989, Appointment telephone procedures manual (Box CH42)
      - 1989, Billing questions (Box CH42)
      - 1989, Centers for Disease Control, 1989: Sexually Transmitted Diseases Treatment Guidelines (Box CH42)
      - circa 1989 and undated, Medical records forms (Box CH42)
      - 1989-1990 and undated, Colposcopy program (Box CH42)
      - 1989-1997, Late second trimester abortion - referrals to Women's Health Care Services (Wichita) (Box CH42)
      - circa 1990, Business Office policies and procedures (Box CH42)
      - 1990-1991, Master manual, 4 folders (Box CH42)
      - 1990-1993, Supervisors' meetings (Box CH43)
      - 1990-1997, Malpractice insurance claims record (Box CH43)
      - 1991 July 9, Directors Meeting minutes (Box CH43)
      - 1991, Clinic utilization statistics (Box CH43)
      - 1991, Gynecology lab results (Box CH43)
      - 1991, Gynecology patient form letters (Box CH43)
      - 1991, Nursing staff meeting notes (Box CH43)
      - 1991-1992, Centralized Laboratory Services (Box CH43)
      - 1991-1994 and undated, Norplant information and policies (Box CH43)
      - 1992 May 14, Sonography issues meeting minutes (Box CH43)
      - 1992, Quality Assurance Committee (Box CH43)
      - 1992, "Signature lists/Policy and Procedure Revisions" (Box CH43)
      - 1992 and undated, Anesthesia providers and costs (Box CH43)
      - 1992 and undated, Front desk manual and reports (Box CH43)
      - 1992-1993, Pharmacy and Therapeutics Committee, minutes and site review reports (Box CH43)
      - 1992-1994, Pre-operative sonography, appeals for insurance and Medicaid reimbursement (Box CH43)
      - 1992-1994 and undated, Medical records forms, revisions and printing costs (Box CH43)
      - 1992-1996, HIV Primary Care Program, 1 of 3 folders (Box CH43)
      - 1992-1996, HIV Primary Care Program, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box CH44)
      - 1992-1996, Mammogram providers (Box CH44)
      - 1992-1998, Universal Diagnostic Laboratories (Box CH44)
      - 1993 Nov.-Dec., Pregnancy tests performed (Box CH44)
      - 1993, Centers for Disease Control, 1993: Sexually Transmitted Diseases Treatment Guidelines (Box CH44)
      - 1993, HIV Primary Care Program proposal (Box CH44)
      - 1993, HIV testing policies (Box CH44)
      - 1993, Planning Committee minutes (Box CH44)
      - 1993, Quality Assurance Committee (Box CH44)
      - 1993-1994, Medical staff meeting minutes (Box CH44)
      - 1993-1994, Men's health services/urology, 2 folders (Box CH44)
      - 1993-1995, Directors Meeting minutes (Box CH45)
      - 1993-1995, Counseling manual - Master Manual, Vol. 4, 2 folders (Box CH45)
      - 1993-1995, Metpath negotiations (Box CH45)
      - 1993-1995 and undated, Appointment room notebook (Box CH45)
      - 1993-1998, Computers (Box CH45)
      - 1994 July 7, "Notes on meeting at Elmhurst" (Box CH45)
      - 1994, Abortion intake procedure and forms (Box CH45)
      - 1994, Quality Assurance Committee (Box CH45)
      - 1994 and undated, Mid-life/menopause women's health program (Box CH45)
      - 1994 and undated, Telephone procedures (Box CH45)
      - 1994-1995, Pharmacy and Therapeutics Committee, minutes and site review reports (Box CH45)
      - 1994-1995, Medical records consultant reports (Box CH45)
      - 1994-1995 and undated, HMO/PPO insurance agreements, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH45)
      - 1994-1995 and undated, HMO/PPO insurance agreements, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH46)
      - 1994-1995 and undated, Voice mail scripts (Box CH46)
      - 1994-1997, Planning Committee minutes, 2 folders (Box CH46)
      - 1994 and 1997, Residency Training Program (Box CH46)
      - 1995, Medical Records Problems notebook, 2 folders (Box CH46)
      - 1995, Quality Assurance Committee (Box CH46)
      - 1995, Therapy case review/utilization review (Box CH46)
      - 1995-1996, Medical staff meeting minutes (Box CH46)
      - 1995-1997, Medical Students for Choice internship (Box CH46)
      - 1996, Committee descriptions (Box CH46)
      - 1996, Directors Meeting minutes (Box CH46)
      - 1996, PPO/HMO meeting minutes (Box CH47)
      - 1996 and undated, CPR training (Box CH47)
      - 1996-1997, Non-surgical abortion procedures (Box CH47)
      - 1996-1997, Pharmacy and Therapeutics Committee, minutes and site review reports (Box CH47)
      - 1996-1998 and undated, Laboratory issues (Box CH47)
      - 1996-1999, Annual reports (Box CH47)
      - 1997 May 14, Continuous Quality Improvement meeting minutes (Box CH47)
      - 1997, CPT and ICD-9-CM training manual (Box CH47)
      - 1997, Directors Meeting minutes (Box CH47)
      - 1997, Information Systems projects (Box CH47)
      - 1997, Managed care consultants - Empire Health Advisors (Box CH47)
      - 1997, Medical procedures draft (Box CH47)
      - 1997-1998, Medical Administration meeting minutes (Box CH47)
      - 1997-1998 and undated, Reference - staff lists and clinic information (Box CH47)
      - 1998 June 2, Medical Advisory Committee minutes (Box CH47)
      - 1998, Consultants' site reviews (Box CH47)
      - 1998, Directors Meeting minutes, 1 of 3 folders (Box CH47)
      - 1998, Directors Meeting minutes, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box CH48)
      - 1998, Information systems - medical billing databases (Box CH48)
      - 1998, Medical Administration meeting minutes (Box CH48)
      - 1998, Medical Advisory Committee mailing list (Box CH48)
      - 1998, Telephone caller ID blocking (Box CH48)
      - 1998 and undated, Information Systems projects (Box CH48)
      - 1998-1999, Continuing Quality Improvement reports (Box CH48)
      - 1999-2000, Directors Meeting minutes (Box CH48)
      - 1990s, Counseling Policies and Procedures Manual (Box CH48)
      - Undated, Forms and flyers (Box CH48)
      - Undated, Men's STD services project (Box CH48)
      - Undated, Physicians training (abortion) - procedures manual (Box CH48)
      - Undated, Policies and procedures (Box CH48)
      - Undated, Quality Assurance audit manual (Box CH48)
  - Electronic Format Subseries, 1985-1999
    Contains numerous Choices documents, including procedural manuals, forms, and other materials concerning the clinic's medical practices and administration.
    Electronic documents have been transferred from their original computer disks to the electronic records server. Files originally located on the same disk have been kept together on the server, in subdirectories labeled by disk number. These disk numbers do not reflect Hoffman's own labels or arrangement of the disks; the numbers were assigned to the original computer disks in the order they were received. This original order has been re-arranged in alphabetical order by supplied title as described below.
    This inventory provides a summary of the contents of each computer disk. It does not list individual electronic files. Computer disks are listed alphabetically. For each disk, a brief descriptive title of the contents is followed by the disk number, the original disk label, and the number of files on the disk.
    There are also a few Choices electronic documents located in mixed-file groups in the Personal Series Electronic Format Subseries.
    For access to the electronic records, please consult with Research Services staff.
    - Administrative records (medical policies, forms, meetings, personnel materials, one Operation Rescue file, one patient questionnaire form), 1989. Disk 006: "#28 DUPLICATE (Mary)", 90 files (Box CH48)
    - Choices flyer, in Chinese, 1998. Disk 073: "PageMaker 718 (21) Mar. 14, 94," in envelope "Page Maker Chinese Second Version", 1 file (Box CH48)
    - Choices flyer in QuarkXPress, 1999. Disk 059: "Ms. Donna L. Helb, 303 Park Ave. S. New York, NY 10010-3601, MAC, CHOICES FLYER (Profile), FONTS: Cochin[?]/Helv. B,1[?]/Times Europa", 12 files (Box CH48)
    - Choices flyer, in Russian, 1998. Disk 071: "Queens Russ. 2," in envelope "Russian Second Version," from American International Translators, 1 file (Box CH48)
    - Choices flyer, in Spanish, 1998. Disk 072: "American Int'l Translating CHOICES Spanish WP 5.1", 1 file (Box CH48)
    - Correspondence, form letters, and mailing lists, 1985-1988. Disk 051: "Disk #7 Merge Letter, New Gyn Pats. Duplicate Disk", 171 files (Box CH48)
    - Directory of D+C physicians, lists of physicians, and lists of community organizations, 1988. Disk 028: "Disk #12, D+C physician list. Duplicate disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 12 files (Box CH48)
    - Employee manual, 1989-1991. Disk 004: "Disk II (Duplicate) Employee Manual", 9 files (Box CH48)
    - Form letters, patient handouts, and other forms, 1986-1991. Disk 049: "#5 Printed Forms + Forms Admin", 225 files (Box CH48)
    - Job descriptions, orientation materials, forms and policies, and other personnel materials, 1989. Disk 003: "Joan Taverni Personnel Disk #22 (copy of disk 22) DUPLICATE", 129 files (Box CH48)
    - Mailing lists and lists of other community organizations, 1986-1988. Disk 027: "Disk 12A, Mailing lists, duplicate copy," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 99 files (Box CH48)
    - Medical records forms and policies, clerical procedures, and vasectomy forms and procedures, 1985-1989. Disk 007: "(copy) #10 Mary's disk", 105 files (Box CH48)
    - Meeting minutes, medical policies, research, and general administrative files, 1986-1989. Disk 044: "Disk 2A, A. Walsh Duplicate Disk", 93 files (Box CH48)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988. Disk 010: "Disk 17, MH, duplicate disk," in box labeled "7/88 15A-20C", 3 files (Box CH48)
    - Outreach report and mailing list, 1998. Disk 066: "Brooklyn Drs." [removed from Kristen Hyduchak files], 4 files (Box CH48)
    - Personnel, correspondence and form letters, 1986-1987. Disk 029: "Disk #13, personnel duplicate copy," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 21 files (Box CH48)
    - Policies and procedures manual, with forms and patient handouts, 1985-1989. Disk 023: "Disk 9A, Policy + Procedures, Duplicate Disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 120 files (Box CH48)
    - Policies and procedures manual, with job descriptions and patient handouts, 1985-1987. Disk 024: "Disk 9B, Pol + Procedures, duplicate disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 224 files (Box CH48)
    - Policies and procedures manual, 1985-1989. Disk 022: "Disk #9, Policy + Procedure Manual, Duplicate Disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 130 files (Box CH48)
    - Policies, forms, Merle Hoffman speech, and Choices East proposal, 1989. Disk 002: "DUPLICATE #24 (Mary)", 42 files (Box CH48)
    - Post-abortion instructions in Spanish and English, 1998. Disk 065: "Post-Ab Instructions f:/admin/postab.wpd a:\post-sp.wpd", 2 files (Box CH48)
    - Procedures manuals and 1986 budget, 1986-1989. Disk 025: "Disk 10, David Smollett, duplicate disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 27 files (Box CH48)
    - Quality Assurance meetings and records, 1989. Disk 001: "#27, DUPLICATE (Mary)", 54 files (Box CH48)
    - Rape Treatment Program materials, 1992. Disk 033: "Sherry --duplicate", 51 files (Box CH48)
    - "Temp Manual," 1987. Disk 026: "Disk #11, Personnel Book, duplicate disk," in box labeled "7/88 7A-14A", 3 files (Box CH48)
    - Unidentified Hindi materials and fonts, 1998. Disk 074: "New Disk Mac (Second Version)," in envelope "2nd rev. - Second Version HINDI" [removed from Patient Information files], 5 files (Box CH48)
- On the Issues Series, 1980-2000 and undated, bulk 1990s, 27 boxes
  Divided into the following subseries: Issues, Correspondence, Article Files, Editorial Files, Marketing, Production and Distribution, Marketing, Staff Files, Administration Subseries, and Electronic Format. Except for the Issues Subseries and the Production and Distribution Subseries, all subseries are organized alphabetically. Editorial and production files are concentrated in the late 1990s. See below for full subseries descriptions.
  On the Issues staff rosters are available for reference in the Research Room's inventory files; please contact Research Services. For additional production materials, see the Photographic Material Series. See the Personal Series for additional materials on Merle Hoffman's writings for On the Issues.
  - Issues Subseries, 1983-1999
    Contains a nearly complete run of On the Issues magazine, arranged chronologically, with two issues missing. On the Issues appeared annually, with some irregularities, from 1983 to 1990. It began quarterly publication in mid-1990. Before mid-1993, each issue was given its own volume number. In 1993, a new series of annual volume numbers was initiated. The first issue in the new series was volume 2, number 3. From 1990 to 1992, the Winter issue was the last issue of the calendar year; from 1994 to 1999, the Winter issue was the first issue of the year. There was no Winter 1993 issue published.
    - 1983 Fall (Vol. 1) (Box OTI1)
    - 1984 Summer/Fall-1993 Spring (Vols. 3 - 26) (Box OTI1)
    - 1993 Summer-1997 Winter (Vol. 2, no. 3 - Vol. 6, no. 1) (Box OTI1)
    - 1997 Summer-1999 Winter (Vol. 6, no. 3 - Vol. 8, no. 1) (Box OTI1)
  - Correspondence Subseries, 1987-2000 and undated
    Folders contain communications regarding the editorial, distribution, business, and advertising aspects of producing the magazine. Arranged alphabetically.
    - Advertisement exchanges, 1997-1998 (Box OTI1)
    - Advertisers, 1997-1998 and undated (Box OTI2)
    - Authors and contributors, 1992-1997 and undated (Box OTI2)
    - Brail, Stephanie (web site), 1995 (Box OTI2)
    - Ciano, Bob (art director), 1994 (Box OTI2)
    - Correspondence and publicity, 1987 (Box OTI2)
    - Direct mail marketing - list rental agencies, 1992-1997 (Box OTI2)
    - Direct mail marketing - Tyson Associates, 1993 (Box OTI2)
    - Distributors, 1988-1999 and undated (Box OTI2)
    - E-mail inquiries - answered, 1998 (Box OTI2)
    - E-mail to answer, 1998 (Box OTI2)
    - General correspondence, 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box OTI2)
    - General correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box OTI3)